Hello friends, I am welcome to
our channel. In today's video,
I am going to tell you how you can
link the traffic light on Amazon to the iMobile application and how
you can link any ICICI credit card to the
iMobile application.
You will get complete information in this video. Let's
start the video. First of all,
what you have to do is download the ICICI mobile
application from the Play Store.
After downloading,
register it. After doing this,
see here you have to
subscribe in many options. After clicking,
you have to click on an option link, credit card
link and
select it here. You have to select the
credit card. Enter the digit number of the credit card
here.
I will click here now.
After this, what you have to do is
fill in your expiry date
and here you will see that your
mobile number and your email ID will already appear in the
field here. After that, you have to
submit it. You will see that the submit
police has been submitted here and here
you will get a service request number and
it will be submitted first.  To track, you have to click on the
team there, go to service and
below you will get the option of take status,
click on check status, then here the
option of track service request comes,
you have to check here, then you will see that the
service request that I have just given is
open, so here, till your service request
is open, it has not been linked yet, so
now you will have to
wait for some time, like 1 to 2 hours,
you will have to wait for three hours, so after three hours
you have to check from here, like
see here, I checked here again,
after 2 hours, my status here is done, that
means my account is
linked,
here you will come to the app,
first of all you have to look here, you will
see that here my
ICICI credit card on Amazon is linked,
so here I will tell you all the details,
you have to click on nude details, if you
click on this stage, then you will
see here that your limit is and like
my limit which is visible here is 70
thousand.  A limit of 70 thousand is visible
and here I have not used any credit till now,
so it is showing zero here,
here you will see that below you will see the
option of manage, if you click on manage then
all the details of the card will be
shown here, due to some security reasons I will
not be able to show you this video completely,
so the process which I have told you,
through prostate you will get all the
details here and you can click on this card which
you have made from Amazon
here, I hope the
information given by me will be useful for you,
if you are not on this channel then
definitely subscribe to the channel, press the bell icon so
that you get to see the latest news.